[ WIND GUSTING ]
[ VEHICLE PASSING ]
[ TIRES SQUEALING ]
Hi . Can I have some mashed potatoes , please ?
No protein ?
No thanks . No meat .
Mm-mm .
MOTHER : What ?
- [ GROANING ] - What 's wrong ?
Spit it out .
- Shit . Did you bite into it ? - No .
- Sure ? - Look . No .
- This shit really gets me . - Mom , it 's fine . Forget it .
Seriously ? And if you were allergic ?
You want mine ?
No , thanks .
MOTHER : My daughter had meat .
It 's unacceptable . We 're vegetarians .
[ INAUDIBLE ]
Wow , it looks shabbier . Don 't you think ?
Is that it ?
No , that 's the med faculty . Hospital on the left , morgue next to it .
And the grocery store , look .
I 'm already lost .
- You have your phone ? - Yeah .
Call your sister . She may answer for you .
I 'm going . She won 't come .
Are you nuts ? We 're not leaving Juju on her own !
She said she 'd pick her up .
- Wait a bit , she may come . - So , brainiac ,
show ' em what you can do . OK ? See you .
- I love you , baby . - Mmm
- Call me . - Yeah .
- Love you too , Mommy . - [ CAR ENGINE STARTS ]
[ MEN SHOUTING AND CHEERING INDISTINCTLY ]
[ BANGING ]
- [ MEN SHOUTING INDISTINCTLY ] - [ DOOR OPENS ]
What 's that shit music ?
- Beats me . Who are you ? - Roommate . I got here late . Up !
- You 're not a girl . - Nope .
- I asked for a girl . - They gave you a fag , same deal for them .
- Here , take this . - What 's going on ? What 's this ?
A ski pole .
- [ DOOR BANGS OPEN ] - [ ALL CLAMORING ]
[ CLAMORING CONTINUES ]
That 's my shit !
Hey ! Where are you going ? Where ?
- Bed , man . - Bed ? Where ? Your bed 's downstairs , friend .
[ LAUGHS ]
Check it . This one wants out already !
You got in to please your parents , right ?
- I thought it was over . - You 'll know if it 's over , big guy .
Get back in line . Get in line .
And now , where are we headed ?
Where ?
- To freedom ! - ADRIEN : Fuck off !
- Fuckers ! - ALL : Speed it up , rookies !
Assholes .
Get up ! Move your asses ! Hurry , the boss is waiting .
- Move it ! - BOY : Come on , guys .
[ ALL CLAMORING ]
Faster , rookies !
Move down !
[ CLAMORING CONTINUES ]
Move your asses ! You ! You stay put .
Go . Go . Move it . Move it .
Rookies , move it !
Get moving , go , go !
Hey , it 's just a game . What do you think could happen ?
I 'm Adrien .
Justine .
[ INAUDIBLE ]
[ UPBEAT MUSIC PLAYING ]
[ INDISTINCT CONVERSATIONS ]
Slut it up , girls .
You 're the slut .
[ ALL LAUGHING AND SHOUTING ]
- [ MUSIC CONTINUES PLAYING ] - [ ALL SHOUTING ]
Alex !
I 'm so wasted .
- Where were you ? - Mom and Dad will kill you .
It 's so cool you 're here . You 'll love it . The first year is the best .
And we 'll see each other all the time , like at home .
Is my thong out of my shorts ?
You 're fine .
- Mom got to you , I see . Was it hell without me ? - What do you mean ?
[ RETCHING ]
Fuck .
I need some fresh air .
Quicky !
Long time , no see !
[ MUSIC CONTINUES PLAYING ]
- JUSTINE : Where 's the light ? - ALEXIA : Don 't . We 're not allowed in here .
JUSTINE : Where are we ?
Alex ?
Where do I go now ?
- [ THUD ] - Fuck , bumped my eye !
- [ SCREAMS ] - [ ALEXIA LAUGHS ]
- Where are you ? - Ugh .
[ ALEXIA LAUGHING ]
- [ HISSES ] - JUSTINE : Stop it !
Look .
- Some heads are cut off . - Traitors . They refused initiation .
Here it is , come look .
Who 's that ?
[ LAUGHS ] No way . They wouldn 't do that kind of thing .
- It 's tradition . You will too , right . - Really ?
- Don 't be a wimp . Even Mom looks happy . - [ BOTH CHUCKLE ]
Poor Dad , it 's all over him . You can 't see his face .
Are you cold ?
I 'm going back to dance . Watch Quicky ?
- I 'm going to bed , I 'm dead . - No way !
- Why ? - Rookies don 't go to bed before us .
[ JUSTINE URGES QUICKY ]
[ SIGHS ]
[ EXHALES ]
[ DOOR OPENS , CLOSES ]
[ BOYS LAUGHING ]
ADRIEN : Shh ! My roommate 's sleeping . Come with me .
[ SIGHS ]
ADRIEN : Wait .
Ketamine .
[ MACHINE WHIRRING ]
Let 's try it .
Move it up .
OK . Take the brace .
A student for the strut , a cushion for the head .
ALL : [ SINGING ] # Vets , they march ahead #
# Their dicks up proud in the air #
# Cuz a vet will fuck you anywhere #
# They are men , yes sir ! With giant balls , for her #
# They like a laugh , they like a drink #
# They like to screw and we do too ! #
# Oh yes , they do , and we do too #
[ GASPS ]
71st graduating class St. Expuery School of Veterinary Medicine , September 2015
SC PRESIDENT : Conscripts !
You have made it to our great school . We applaud you .
Your profs will make you the best vets out there .
Your elders will make you family .
But first you must learn .
Learn to be a team , to obey , to be good rookies .
From now on , you will call your elders either " elders " or " great ones " .
Repeat after me : Elders .
- ALL : Elders . - Hey ! Elders .
ALL : Elders .
Good . And great ones .
ALL : Great ones .
SC PRESIDENT : What a nice bunch this year . Where was I ?
They 'll help you during your rush week , which will end when you hear this :
For real ?
- When you hear . Yeah . - [ BLOWS AIR HORN ]
Then and only then are you no longer rookies . In the meantime , we 're counting on you .
Make us proud . We 'll show you the way .
Vets !
[ SPITS ]
[ INDISTINCT CHATTERING ]
ADRIEN : Longest wait ever for an open bar .
What is it ?
- Wait your turn . - Is it meat ?
- Rabbit kidney . Better not to know . - I 'm a vegetarian , I can 't eat that .
Ask my sister , our family 's veggie .
- Who 's your sister ? - Alexia .
No shit .
- Alex ? Alex , come here a sec . - Huh ?
- You vegetarian ? - No . Why ?
She your sister ?
Call my parents if you don 't trust me .
Are you serious ? It 's nothing . Everybody does it .
- So eat hers then . - ALEXIA : I ate mine last year .
That 's why I 'm here now .
Go on , eat it .
[ SIGHS ]
See ? Easy .
Open up .
You 'll be happy you did it .
Don 't start the year by chickening out . They 're watching .
[ COUGHS ]
[ RETCHES ]
[ BREATHING HEAVILY ]
Maybe not all animals , but monkeys .
It comes from them .
Do you think a monkey can get AIDS today ?
If you treat a monkey in a zoo or African reserve ,
are you as careful as a doctor doing normal surgery ?
- No clue . Why are you thinking about this shit ? - Take a guy who wants to fuck a monkey .
The theory is AIDS started that way . If a guy wants to fuck a monkey today ,
should he use a condom ?
I 'm eating , man ! Don 't talk about fucking monkeys .
Did wolves raise you ?
What do I care ?
Cuz I fuck monkeys or have AIDS ?
What the fuck .
OK , sorry . It was a valid question .
They only ate monkeys . The rest was made up .
- Who 'd be so sick he 'd rape an animal ? - Lots of people .
- Legally , I 'm not sure " monkey rape " exists . - Sure it does . Animals have rights .
The monkey won 't turn anorexic and see a therapist . It 's not the same .
Monkeys are self-aware .
They see themselves , in a mirror , right ?
- I bet a raped monkey suffers like a woman . - GIRL : So a raped woman ,
raped monkey , same thing ?
Yeah .
What I 'm saying isn 't so crazy . Why are we in vet school ?
Unbelievable .
It 's easy , really .
I expected no less from you .
Let 's see if your reputation is earned .
Oh .
One mistake already . Off to a bad start .
- May I ? - No . Too late .
There .
[ SCRATCHING ]
[ SIGHS ]
[ YELPS ]
[ BREATHING HEAVILY ]
[ KNOCK ON DOOR ]
- ADRIEN : Hey . Are you OK ? - Yeah . Stay out .
[ GASPS , BREATHING HEAVILY ]
[ WINCES ]
[ BLOWS ]
[ SIGHS ]
[ STOMACH GURGLES ]
[ BREATHING HEAVILY ]
Oh , that is bad . Any allergies ?
- I don 't think so . - OK .
Will I get it on my face ?
No , no . It won 't last long . It 's already peeling .
- Any nausea ? - Yeah .
Since when ?
- At the same time . - OK . Last period ?
[ WINCES ]
I 'm not sure . A week or two ?
- OK . Are you on the pill ? - No .
- [ WINCES ] - Do you use condoms ?
I 've never ...
Right .
OK .
Yeah , yeah , yeah , yeah .
And this is your rush week ?
OK . I think it 's food poisoning and you 're having a reaction .
Drink lots of liquids . Water , that is . Avoid solids . Fast a whole day , even .
I 'll get you a cream .
I am hungry though . My stomach always feels empty .
Yeah .
- What 'd they give you ? - Raw rabbit kidneys .
Someone tells you to eat raw rabbit kidney , and you do ?
- I said no . - Did they force you ?
- No . - OK . Keep it .
- Use it three times a day . - Thanks .
I used to work at the hospital here .
One day , they sent a girl your age for blood tests .
She was round .
- [ LIGHTER CLICKS ] - Mmm .
Fat , actually .
A really nice girl , really sweet . Some freak out over needles , but not her . Mmm .
She had a ton of tests to do .
So it goes well .
She gets dressed and bursts into tears .
I ask what 's wrong and she says I 'm the first person to not mention her weight .
Why would I ?
The test was totally unrelated .
She said the interns sent her ward to ward ,
saying they couldn 't jab her due to the fat on her arms .
They said to lose weight and come back .
Can you imagine ? Nonsense . I 'd had no trouble finding a vein .
Why didn 't she report it ?
Why ? Don 't know . To not bother anyone , I guess .
She kind of stood out . She probably wanted to be average .
How do you see yourself ?
- Average . - [ SCOFFS ]
Find yourself a quiet corner . Wait it out . The year always starts out rough .
[ INDISTINCT CONVERSATIONS ]
Eyes to the floor for an elder , rookie !
- You wearing that ? You didn 't hear today ? - Hear what ?
The dress code is night club . Go change .
Girls wear something hot . Not t-shirts with sequins .
This is all I have .
- Is that a no ? - I 'll have to look .
OK . Uniform then .
[ PROFESSOR TALKING INDISTINCTLY ]
Yes ? Come in . Hurry up .
Here you have the septate uterus , characterized by its long horns
and gradual narrowing toward the fallopian tubes .
Too small .
No way you 're having that .
If you 'd spoken up , I wouldn 't have had to eat it .
Let it go ! It was that or you were a reject .
It 's your life ! I shouldn 't have helped .
You didn 't !
[ SIGHS ]
I 'm being nice . You 'll stretch them with your big feet .
Come here ! I 'm not your slave !
- Your handwriting is awful . - What ?
Do you write on the washer ?
Hands off !
I just fixed a couple things . Small errors , mostly .
Take what you need and scram .
- Move . - Can I try it on ?
Quick .
[ EXHALES ]
It 's not me .
OK , get out .
- Like this ? - Yeah .
You piss me off .
See you .
[ SIGHS ]
[ STRAINING ]
Fuck this !
- [ SIGHS ] - [ SHOES CLATTERING ]
Could you help me with ...
- ADRIEN : Don 't stop . So good . - [ ADRIEN SIGHING DEEPLY ]
[ ADRIEN MOANING ]
- That 's pork . - So ?
Grab some ketchup .
- What 's in your pocket ? - Sorry ?
- Your lab coat . There . Show me . - Problem solved .
I need to see to ring it up .
[ CASH REGISTER BEEPS ]
Stealing a burger 's fucked up , even for me . You need cash ?
Did anyone see ?
Nah . Own it . Why that ?
[ SNAPS FINGERS ]
Don 't know .
- I 'm starving . It 'll be awesome . - It 's stupid .
It 's a first , we need to celebrate .
- It 's on me . - [
CHUCKLES ] Great .
ADRIEN : What 's your sister 's problem ?
- JUSTINE : What problem ? - ADRIEN : Let 's sit over there .
I don 't know , she 's not exactly friendly .
JUSTINE : What do you know ? You barely talk to her .
ADRIEN : Neither have you , since you arrived .
I can 't if you watch .
Say that you kill a guy 's hard-on for life .
It 's so bullshit to sell booze at rest stops . Check the bigwigs .
Big rigs , you mean . Wig 's different . Big wigs are like VIPs or something .
OK . Even with an hour 's sleep , you 're still drunk .
Do you think they swap blood or inject water , like cyclists ?
Ask him yourself .
MAN : Where you kids off to ?
Just having some shawarma . Then back to campus .
You 're at the vet school ?
I came down there once with my pig , he had the flu .
Flu 's bad for pigs . But he 's better now .
- You have a pig in your truck ? - Yeah .
We all do . To swap our boozer blood .
Pigs are almost like humans . Have you learned that yet ?
Genetically , or something .
Well kiddos , enjoy your meal .
Little lady 's hungry . Don 't they feed you down there ?
School 's good . You 're lucky .
You 're up ?
For breakfast .
- Putting on a barbecue ? - [ CHUCKLES ]
What do you eat ?
Cereal .
- Cereal 's up there . - I 'm just getting milk , OK ?
[ DOOR OPENS , CLOSES ]
[ GRUNTS ]
- PROFESSOR : So you cheated . - No .
- You admit your friend did . - No .
Miss , I don 't have a soft spot for top students , unlike all my colleagues ,
I feel more sympathy for your friend than you .
School is tough for him . He has to fight to stay .
But you ,
the wonder child , you ride in and depress my students .
Some would sooner drop out than compare themselves to you .
You aren 't needed here .
Worse , you scare away excellent doctors .
As you can guess , I 'd rather see your ranking drop than your friend 's .
It was him .
[ RETCHING ]
[ GAGGING ]
[ COUGHING ]
[ COUGHS ]
[ GAGGING , COUGHING ]
[ GASPING ]
[ COUGHING ]
[ SPITS ]
[ BREATHING HEAVILY ]
[ COUGHS ]
Two fingers will make it come up faster .
[ DOOR CLOSES ]
[ COW MOOS ]
Alex !
- Hey ! - [ COWS MOOING ]
Alex ! Alex !
Can we talk ?
- Can 't hear you ! - We have to talk .
Afterwards !
[ COWS CONTINUE MOOING ]
- One time I made out with a one-armed guy . - No way .
Yeah . [ LAUGHING ] It took me two hours to notice .
You know , he draped a blazer over his shoulder . I thought , OK , country club , must have money .
But no , he just had one arm . [ LAUGHS ]
- Alex ? - Mmm ?
Do you think I 'm weird ?
What ? No ! Why ?
You know you 're the favorite .
I 'm the weirdo in the family . Always have been .
[ JUSTINE LAUGHS ]
What are you doing ? What the fuck ?
Hips pushed out , see . And go ! No hands .
- How do you do that ? - Go on , let 's see how far you shoot .
Push hard to get a strong stream and it works .
- I 'll go all over myself . - [ BOTH LAUGHING ]
Deep breath ...
Fuck ! I 'm pissing on myself !
Normal squat ! Normal squat !
I 'm still peeing .
[ BOTH LAUGHING ]
Damn !
So gross .
Let 's go , it 's raining .
Can I sleep over ? I don 't feel well .
You never feel well , ever .
What ? What 's wrong ?
Stay still .
Better ?
Looks the same to me .
- At your age , I already gave myself Brazilians . - What 's that ?
- [ WINCES ] It 's scorching . Will it hurt a lot ? - Beauty is pain .
- [ SCREAMS ] - [ EXCLAIMS ]
- [ GROANS ] - I 'm amazing .
- No , I can 't . - And leave it like that ?
- It 's uneven . - No , this is torture .
Great , now it 's worse . Let me do the other side at least .
Tell me when you 're ... Ow !
[ LAUGHS ]
- No ! No ! - Come on . We all do it .
[ WINCES ]
- [ YELPS ] - Shit .
What ? Tell me .
- Odd . It 's stuck . - It 's stuck ?
- I don 't know . - What 's Plan B ?
This is weird . Wait .
Get away !
- No , no , you 'll circumcise me ! - We have to .
You 're shaking .
It 's my pussy !
What ?
What ? What is it ?
[ BREATHING SHAKILY ]
Alex ! Alex ! Hey ! Hey !
Hey ! Hey !
My sister cut her finger .
With scissors .
Cutting something , who cares !
15 minutes ?
Ice ? OK , I know .
OK .
[ BREATHING HEAVILY ]
[ EXHALES ]
[ LAUGHING SOFTLY ]
- Anyone seen you for the prosthesis ? - What ?
- Didn 't they sew it back on ? - ALEXIA : Nope .
Quicky ate my finger .
FATHER : The doctor will be by soon .
MOTHER : What about her rehab ? How does it work ?
No nerve damage , no rehab . There 's no point .
You 're leaving her like this ? Really ? She can 't eat !
- I 'm not disabled . - Yes , you are !
- ALEXIA : You 'd like that ! - MOTHER : Don 't say that .
Shit , leave her alone !
Don 't talk to your mother that way . What 's wrong ?
- I 'm going to piss . - Me too .
What the hell ? OW .
- [ WHEELCHAIR THUDS ] - ALEXIA : Ouch !
[ PANTING ]
[ GAGS , COUGHS ]
[ COUGHS ]
[ COUGHING ]
Apologize to your mother .
I 'm not going back in there .
- Do you smoke ? - Yeah .
- Who has Quicky ? - [ LAUGHS ] He 'll be put down , if not already .
Why ? He didn 't attack her . That 's cruel !
They have to . An animal that has tasted human flesh isn 't safe .
If he likes it , he 'll bite again .
Can 't he just take a pill ?
Medicine 's not an exact science . You 'll see .
[ SIGHS ]
Don 't have two girls , honey . It 's too hard .
ALEXIA : Mom and Dad still here ?
JUSTINE : No .
- JUSTINE : Where are you going ? - ALEXIA : We ... we need to talk .
Here 's good .
- You wanted to talk ? - What about ?
- You asked . - Something to say ?
- No , you brought me out here . - So ?
I 've nothing to say .
Stop mind fucking me then ! You 're like Mom !
You sound like Mom .
If we 're here for deer , I 'll kill you .
- You 're so aggressive . - JUSTINE : No , I 'm not .
Anger management issues !
- I 'm not angry ! - Stay here !
Alex !
- [ TIRES SQUEALING ] - [ CAR CRASHES ]
[ HORN BLARING CONTINUOUSLY ]
Alex ?
- Are you OK ? - [ GROANS ]
[ HORN CONTINUES BLARING ]
What 's wrong with you ?
Nice , yell at me now .
Shit .
[ EXHALES SHARPLY ]
Don 't ! What are you doing ?
Stop .
Why are you opening the door ?
[ PANTING ]
He won 't make it .
Spit it out !
I said , spit !
Fuck ! Are you kidding ?
I did this for you , idiot !
You need to learn , right ?
[ BREATHING HEAVILY ]
[ CAR HORN BLARES ]
[ INDISTINCT CONVERSATIONS ]
What did I miss ?
Do me up .
Done ?
It 's the gloves .
- Take them off . - PROFESSOR : Remove the sheet .
We 're starting .
Geez . What a pain .
You may begin . You have an hour .
- Sorry for your sis . - No shit . I thought you hated her .
- It 's still fucked . - It 's just a finger .
PROFESSOR : Very nice .
Look , get right in there . Dive in , don 't be afraid .
Tell her . She 'll like that .
ALL : [ SINGING ] # Rookies , we got lucky #
# We 're here , it 's going to get yucky #
# Watch out , rookie #
# Don 't refuse , everyone must pay their dues #
- Rookies ! - SENIORS : Sit !
[ ALL CLAMORING ]
- Rookies ! - SENIORS : Stand !
- SC PRESIDENT : Rookies ! - SENIORS : Sing !
ALL : [ SINGING ] # Help me , help me , the rabbit said #
# Or the hunter will shoot me dead #
[ SENIORS BOOING ]
Bring it down !
Whoo !
[ INAUDIBLE ]
Did you touch it ?
Did you ?
[ INDISTINCT ARGUING ]
You 're insane , man .
- Let 's play , come on . - Over here .
[ SONG PLAYING ON EARPHONES ]
# Seduction 101 be a whore with decorum #
# Laugh at boys ride with poise #
# Blow job queen , give him what he needs #
# Citric acid , pheromonesn Tick tick tick metronomes #
# 1 2 3 4 STOP ! We 're done #
# I 'll treat you good , hurt you good #
# Oops goodbye , ugly dicks with me don 't fly #
# Wedding night I 'll drown you in my pool #
# Suck ya bones , lap it up , honey #
# Go work out #
# Pretty corpse I like to bang the dead #
# Cold and hard , talk less , ' tard #
# I like to bang the dead , bang the dead #
# Drugs yes please Kitten I love you for the grams #
# Dolly Titty Nero so girly #
# Taste the poison lucky charms #
# Bang you pretty boy , my heart ain 't dirty #
# Fun in my sheets , Me + guys = zero #
# Dom + straw = love me #
# We don 't do porn , but we like strap-ons #
# I say tongue , you do clit I say anthrax , you do cash #
# I like coke in kilograms Your friend can keep his kiss #
# Working boy tombstone joy #
# Lord of darkness in my heart bat tattoo #
# Dance for me , oui oui Chucky oui oui #
# Fuck 69 Give me 666 #
# Hey #
# Fuck 69 #
[ VIDEO GAME NOISES ]
[ INDISTINCT CHATTERING ]
- Bam ! Done . - You play 10 to 9 , no wonder .
Cute ! Got my cocktail dress on .
Off to get deflowered at your prom ?
I 'm off .
- JUSTINE AND ALEXIA : Where to ? - Hospital party . It 's hardcore .
They party on call and barf if someone comes in .
They treat the guy , then go back .
Luckily , you had nothing to sew back on . It 'd be on backwards .
- I 'm so lucky . - ADRIEN : Later .
Wanna beat me ?
Hands off .
I thought he was gay .
You want to play ?
Yeah .
Did you lose weight ?
My dress fits you better . It 's less slutty .
Thank you .
It 's not a compliment . You better not be anorexic . It 's gross .
I 'm not sick .
You will be if you keep it up . I know what happens . You won 't hold up .
- I 'm not you . Do your thing . I don 't need that . - Really .
No . I just tried it .
You couldn 't try something other than my finger ?
Nothing else on the menu looked good ?
Was it good at least ?
You taste like curry .
Throw the grenade , throw the grenade !
No , no , you missed it !
Kill yourself , kill yourself .
[ EXPLOSION IN VIDEO GAME ]
[ BREATHING HEAVILY ]
[ METAL CLINKING ]
Alex ?
[ METAL CONTINUES CLINKING ]
- [ THUD ] - [ SCREAMS ]
[ PANTING ]
[ SCREAMS ]
[ SCREAMING ]
Stop !
Alex !
[ SCREAMING ]
[ SCREAMS ]
[ GASPING ]
[ SOBBING SOFTLY ]
- [ MUSIC PLAYING IN DISTANCE ] - [ INDISTINCT CHATTERING ]
[ MUSIC PLAYING LOUDER ]
JUSTINE : Thanks .
Yeah , that one . The yellow one .
Wait , forget it . This 'll do .
Let 's go . Don 't come out until you 're green .
[ MUSIC CONTINUES PLAYING ]
Come here .
It 's OK , we 'll go slow .
- [ INDISTINCT CHATTERING ] - [ VINNIE SCREAMS ]
- [ YELLS ] - [ MUSIC STOPS ]
- Fuck ! What 's wrong ? - She 's fucking insane .
[ ALL MURMURING INDISTINCTLY ]
[ SPITTING ]
[ BREATHING HEAVILY ]
[ DOOR OPENS ]
Want a drag ?
Come here .
Wait .
Did he grab you ?
Yeah , but still .
- He didn 't force you . - [ SCOFFS ] No .
- You like him ? - I don 't know .
- He turns you on . - I don 't know .
- You still turned on now ? - Why do you ask ?
- To figure out how you work . - How I work ?
If you like SM shit , or worse .
- Are you going to kiss me ? - No .
So why stress out ?
I 'm not .
Should I be ?
OK . I 'm tired . I 'm going to bed .
[ DOOR CLOSES ]
It 's bad .
[ GRUNTS ]
[ BREATHING HEAVILY ]
[ GROANS ]
[ WINCES , MOANS ]
[ BOTH BREATHING HEAVILY ]
[ JUSTINE BREATHING HEAVILY ]
Stop it .
Stop it !
[ GROANS ]
[ BREATHING HEAVILY ]
[ MOANING ]
[ CONTINUES MOANING ]
[ BREATHING DEEPLY ]
[ CELL PHONE VIBRATES ]
Tell my sister to look at her phone . Alex .
Mom says they put Quicky down . She 's so sad . LOL # waytoocute
My sister has your number ?
[ CELL PHONE VIBRATES ]
[ SCOFFS ]
Sure . Ignore me .
Nice way to treat a girl after deflowering her . Makes me feel great .
- Screw your sister ! - It 's not about my sister .
Did something happen ?
I 'm sorry . We ... I shouldn 't have done that with you .
What do you mean ? Cut the crap . It 's my fault now ?
Oh , so , I 'm too crazy ?
I 'm gay . OK ? If I spent 20 years hiding , it 's not to fuck girls now , OK ?
[ CHAIR RATTLES ]
[ INAUDIBLE ]
[ UPBEAT MUSIC PLAYING ON SPEAKERS ]
Hey ! Come here , come here .
One shot , please .
- I 'm out of glasses , is that OK ? - A small one .
- Yeah , sure . - Here .
More . More , more . More , more . Save me the trip .
[ LAUGHS ]
Find someone else , bitch !
What 's her problem ?
What are you doing here ?
- They 're no fun . - Let 's split .
Stick around . We 're funny for sure .
Oh yeah , for sure .
ALEXIA : Come on .
[ SNORING SOFTLY ]
[ SIGHS ]
[ INDISTINCT CHATTERING ]
[ SNIFFS ]
Come here . We need to talk .
JUSTINE : What ?
Got something to say ?
What is it ?
[ VIDEO PLAYING INDISTINCTLY ]
GIRL : [ ON VIDEO ] Go fetch !
[ INDISTINCT CHATTERING ]
Go , go , go !
She 's so fucked up . Don 't film it , come on !
[ ALL CLAMORING AND SHOUTING ]
Hey ! Bite .
- Go on . - [ ALL CHEERING ]
Bite him , Justine !
[ ALL CHEERING ON VIDEO ]
GIRL : This is fucked up , stop it .
Where were you ?
You let her do that ?
Wait . Stop , calm down .
Move . Let me go .
- Calm down now . - Get out of my way !
- Stop it , fuck . - Fuck off .
Fuck it , it 's your life .
[ INDISTINCT CONVERSATIONS ]
[ GRUNTS ]
[ ALEXIA GROANS ]
[ JUSTINE SCREAMS ]
[ SPITS ]
You taste like shit .
[ JUSTINE GROANS ]
- GIRL : Are you OK ? - Move .
[ SCREAMS ]
[ BOTH STRUGGLING ]
[ BOTH GRUNTING ]
[ BOTH BREATHING HEAVILY ]
[ SCREAMS ]
[ ALL CLAMORING ]
[ WINCES ]
[ GRUNTS ]
Hey .
Yeah .
[ DOOR CLOSES ]
[ AIR HORN BLOWING ]
[ MUSIC PLAYING ]
[ MUSIC CONTINUES PLAYING IN DISTANCE ]
[ WINCES ]
[ SIGHS ]
[ GASPS ]
[ SCREAMS ]
Adrien ! Adrien !
[ SCREAMING ]
Adrien !
[
SOBBING ] Adrien !
[ GASPING ]
Why didn 't you fight back ?
Hit me !
You should have hit me .
[ CONTINUES SOBBING ]
[ GASPS ]
[ KNOCKS ]
[ DOOR OPENS ]
[ DOOR CLOSES , BEEPS ]
Finish your veggies .
I 'm full .
Don 't leave the table until you 're done .
- Don 't take it personally . - I know .
It 's not your fault .
I know , Dad .
Or your sister 's .
What ?
[ SIGHS ]
When she was born , she was our little princess .
We took her everywhere .
Our friends loved her .
She was full tilt from the start .
She should have studied politics or something . [ CHUCKLES ]
So , I guess she got used to being ...
herself .
It 's our fault . We didn 't find a solution .
What do you mean ?
Your mom was tough at first . Kept saying I was her best friend at school . It drove me nuts .
It 's not like she had a boyfriend . Just me .
And then we had our first kiss . And I understood .
[ GASPS , SNIFFLES ]
I 'm sure you 'll find a solution , honey .